# Akshat Gupta

#### Student Developer

I am an experienced programmer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. I'm skilled in C++, HTML and Python. I feel I am a strong business development professional with an aim to collaborate in Web Development related projects and explore the field of Machine Learning. I am also interested and experienced in Digital Marketing.



- akshatvg23@gmail.com
- Chennai, India
- in linkedin.com/in/akshatvg
- f facebook.com/akshatvg
- akshatvg
- instagram.com/akshatvg

- 9600093179
- akshatvg.com
- @akshatvg
- github.com/akshatvg
- № medium.com/@akshatvg

# **EDUCATION**

# High School

Chinmaya Vidyalaya

05/2009 - 05/2018

Courses

 PCM with Computer Science

#### University

Vellore Institute of Technology, Vellore

06/2018 – Present

Courses

Information Technology

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Member of Digital Marketing Team** Developer Student Clubs VIT

12/2018 – Present

06/2019 - Present

Tacke

 Incharge of chapter's social media channels which includes ideating, planning, coordination and posting content on Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Instagram (stories as well as posts).

Contact: Samarth Nayyar - +91 98182 88112

# Member of SEO Team

Devfest '19 by DSC VIT

Tasks

 Incharge of Search Engine Optimisation for upcoming Hackathon.

Contact: Samarth Nayyar - +91 98182 88112

### **SKILLS**

Leadership

Гeamwork

**Public Speaking** 

HTML/ CSS/ JavaScript/ Bootstrap

WordPress

Medium

SEO

Digital Marketing

Management

### **PROJECTS**

Common Entry Test (01/2019 – Present)

 Web Application to make club and chapter recruitments easier in VIT.

magiCode (05/2019 - 06/2019)

 Voice to Code educative assistant to help migrate to new programming languages. Won IBM Challenge at AngelHack Bangalore 2019.

AAGS- Warehouse Management System (03/2019 – 03/2019)

Project to make an intelligent warehouse management system.
 Won VinHack 2019.

### **ORGANIZATIONS**

Developer Student Clubs VIT (12/2018 – Present) Project Manager

CodeChef-VIT (12/2018 - Present)

Technical Member

Apple Developers Group (12/2018 – Present)

Technical Member

Model United Nations Society VIT (12/2018 – 06/2019)

Core Member

# **LANGUAGES**

English

Hindi

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Tamil

Limited Working Proficiency